[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "How is your family coping with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Very privately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What kind of girl was Olivia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "She was a warm -- she was outgoing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Olivia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What does this say about America that this is happening, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I think that this isn't only about America, I think this is part of the human condition.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Is it any comfort at all to the family, to Olivia's parents, Brian and Shannon, that the whole world is grieving with them and for them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Yes, the Facebook page we put up -- they didn't ask for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian", "Shannon"], "LOCATION": ["Olivia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What is your view about this debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I have to tell you, I don't consider myself an expert and I didn't think that that's the kind of thing that you want me on the show for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "ORGAN: You didn't have any place in civilian hands in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "I have to say -- I'd have to say no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ":", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Can you try and explain to me why you believe the answer to this is to arm teachers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, the alternative is what we have seen, where people were reduced to waiting to be murdered, without able -- being able to do anything effective to protect themselves or the adults, to protect the children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Why where the teachers put the guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "People can carry firearms in a concealed fashion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "It is this, why do you believe, given that you have 300 million guns in circulation and the worst gun crime rate in any of the civilized countries of the world, that more guns is the answer to less gun murder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Because the problem occurs, sir, in those areas precisely where we have said no guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Fairfax County", "America"]}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 165, "question": "From guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "It's under three for 100,000 and in Fairfax County where Gun Owners of America is located --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I think we need to ban gun control laws that keep people from being able to protect themselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "You're an unbelievably stupid man, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "It seems to me that you're morally obtuse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "NNPS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 211, "question": "It seems to me that facts don't bother you, do they, Mr. Morgan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "-- is the right for any -- Americans -- you would like to see --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "How many -- how many guns did Mrs. Lanza have in her home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I don't know how many she had.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNPS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And you would be quite happy if there are many more people in his position, in homes around America, where there are that number of firearms, which could be used by mentally unstable people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Americans with firearms in their homes typically have them locked in a safe.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "How can you say such a thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Let me finish my sentence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Is that the solution to America's gun murder problems?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I would challenge you to go and tell the Korean merchants who survived the riots in Los Angeles, sorry, you had those firearms that saved your lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Can you answer my question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I'm answering your question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Well, the press tend to do that, don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Stop being so facetious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Post what happened at Sandy Hook, your answer to this problem of repeated use of this weapon with these high-capacity magazines is to continue letting Americans buy them with impunity, and to not concern yourself with these mass shootings, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNPS", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "The Second Amendment means what it says, and meanwhile, you want to continue laws against self-defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandy Hook"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Carolyn McCarthy, when you hear this and you hear the way that debate is framed, what is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, to be very honest with you, I'm very happy that you had him on, because I think America should see what we're up against and the lies that they take to the American people, and unfortunately, an awful lot of them believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carolyn McCarthy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Or are other Americans going to rise up and say enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, I believe this terrible tragedy, taking the lives of 20 little people, the same age as my two youngest granddaughters, has affected America in such a deep way, that we're in a position to have, not just a discussion, but the action that I think is necessary to prevent a reoccurrence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Or is it just going to be another statistic in the mass shooting catalog, which is getting worse and worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I think you're right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "How do you change the mentality that says really any American, as Mr. Pratt, believes -- the answer to any of these shootings is to arm everybody else with the same kind of weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "See, I don't think it's the American culture.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Where are those politicians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "They are around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Could that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What was your experience like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Well, two main things in my mind dominated the conversation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121218pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "From that what we know about his profile, what do you think has happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, the common thread, going beyond what you talked about, is that there is a motive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]